Guide to the Buffalo AFL-CIO Council Miscellaneous Documents 1937-1958
Buffalo AFL-CIO Council Miscellaneous Documents
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Buffalo AFL-CIO Council Miscellaneous Documents, 1937-1958
5453
Buffalo AFL-CIO Council
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Records of the Buffalo AFL-CIO Council.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection is arranged in four series: Proceedings, American Labor Party (ALP), Political Action Committees (PAC), and Miscellaneous Documents.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO. Buffalo Council.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Proceedings
Series II. American Labor Party (ALP)
Series III. Political Action Committees (PAC)
Series IV. Miscellaneous Documents
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Proceedings
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Note - Some say "Proceeding of the Executive Board of
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings. Buffalo Federation of Labor, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Series II. American Labor Party (ALP)
  - ALP, 1942-1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Badly folded
  - ALP, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Correspondence
  - ALP, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ALP, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Series III. Political Action Committees (PAC)
  - PAC, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Political Action Ward Clubs, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PAC, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, newspaper clippings
  - Publicity - Local PAC, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Newspaper clippings
  - Publicity - National PAC, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PAC Slingers etc., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Election materials
  - PAC, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Syracuse "Political Street Guide" and "Erie and Niagara Superway"
  - Political Street Guide: Syracuse, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - PAC, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - PAC Office Records, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - UAW Political Action, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - PAC Workers, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Handwritten correspondence
  - PAC Council, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - PAC Council, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - PAC, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - PAC Current Material, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, election propaganda material
  - PAC, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Newspapers, correspondence
  - PAC, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Newspaper articles, correspondence enclosed
  - National PAC, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - PAC, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Correspondence and election brochures
  - Niagara Frontier PAC: Financial Statement, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - PAC, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Series IV. Miscellaneous Documents
  - Political Periodicals, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Correspondence included
  - Presidential Election, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Raffle Book Record, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Magazines/Newspapers, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Note-raffle ticket books also enclosed
  - Niagara Frontier PAC, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Various correspondence
  - Niagara Frontier PAC, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - PAC Convention, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - PAC Request for Endorsement, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - PAC Credential Forms, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate Credential Forms, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - PAC Finances, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Financial information, correspondence
  - PAC, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Various newsletters, correspondence
  - Western New York CIO-PAC, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Various correspondence, receipt book enclosed
  - Central Labor Council, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Monthly record by trade, by local attendance or payment?
  - Election results, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Contains various newspaper clippings
  - Scrap Book, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Newspaper clippings from "Buffalo Federation of Labor News"